Seino! Galgal Channel GOGO!
Today's project is
Learn and dance in 30 minutes!
Last time, Claire and I
Towa-chan and Minami to teach us how to dance idols in 30 minutes.
And they learned a lot!
And Kira-chan
First challenge!
It's my first try.
It's my first time too.
That's right.
Some girls have a reputation for memorizing choreography.
They say you're quick.
That's what they say.
I'd like to give it a try today.
I don't know anything yet.
I really don't know anything.
I don't know what genre it is.
I don't know what kind of music it is.
I don't know if I can do it.
I'll do my best.
I'm a professional.
Please ask me.
I'm listening.
Then let's hear it.
What song?
Lucky Lucky's new song.
Wow, seriously, not "all the way, all the time"?
This one's better, Massa.
I saw it at the event, but it was only one time, and it was from the back...
Wow, the old days are so good.
I didn't see the point dance because there are too many people in the sports formation.
And by the way, I'll tell you what.
I've never heard of it or seen it.
That's not true. It's not like I haven't checked it out or anything.
It's just that I hadn't seen it yet.
It's brand new.
I really liked the lyrics.
I don't remember the dancing, not even yesterday.
What kind? What kind?
It's a ballad.
Well, actually, it's snowing on the day of the shoot.
Yes, it is.
Maybe it's perfect.
It's all clean.
Rust
Oh!
Oh
Yes, yes, yes.
The hand gestures match the lyrics well.
It's complicated.
It really is.
30 minutes?
It's not that long.
It's a nice song.
Well, goodbye.
I'm too motivated.
Okay, 30 minutes.
Okay, now reverse and slow down, please... I just had him reverse, slow down, and slow down, so his voice is a little low.
Let's remember this much.
Left, right.
Left, right? Chan chan chan chan ... Try it for a second.
Choo-choo choo-choo choo-choo choo-choo choo-choo.
Seven.
...eight.
I don't understand this.
Here we go.
That's good choreography.
It's good, isn't it? Pace.
I'm done.
It's not over.
Four.
Breasts!
I'm going to hug you, I'm going to hug you, I'm going to hug you, I'm going to hug you, I'm going to hug you....
Exibiru cedar
I got it, I got it, I got it
good, good, good, good, good
That was fast.
That's good.
It's fast.
You get used to it.
You ready? Mm-hmm.
Mmm.
The end.
This one's a little slow and structured again.
Oh, my God. I've got a glimmer of hope. I see hope, but it's a little complicated... with the hand gestures.
I'm sorry, you know what I mean? You know what I'm talking about? Your hands are so detailed.
Did you put a structure on it?
Composition.
Yes, I did.
Let's put it on already.
I want to show Yotchan that I have a little bit of time to spare.
Yes, a little.
I want to show you.
Oh, like on your back.
That's nice.
Janky janky janky janky janky janky janky janky janky janky janky janky janky janky janky janky janky. In the legs, that's good.
Duncha-duncha-duncha-duncha-duncha-duncha-duncha-duncha.
Duncha-la-la-la-la-la-la.
Dalala la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
Dum-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum.
Sure thing.
Or...
This place could still be all of them once they're here.
This is the first place they'll show us.
And...
Oh, I mean...
That's how we're going to do it?
Oh, it's like this, right?
Like this?
Like that? Oh, I hit it this way, this way. Like this? Like this? Swipe?
I got it this way.
Oh, this way.
Oh, my God, that's a lot.
And there's Mi in front.
Okay, okay.
And she's in front of me.
Misaki is really one step in front
OK
Misaki stays in front.
She's doing a great job of shinning.
Oh, that's good, isn't it?
Let's do it with sound.
Oh, here comes the next preview... we're going to dye the fresh sky... even if it's still vague... we're going to draw it...
We'll run together, we'll run together, we'll run together.
I'll dye the blank map
We'll never get lost.
One small step can change
Our tomorrow
It's a good idea.
What do you think?
We made it! The challenge succeeded!
Yes, it's a success!
So, I learned and danced it in 30 minutes, and it was a success!
It's cold
Well, it's already snowing so much!
It's really cold!
We suddenly included a lovey-dovey scene...
How did you like it?
Today, I'd like to play Lucky's song.
I danced to Lucky's song in the snowstorm.
If you are a Lucky girl, please go to YouTube and dance to Lucky's song.
Please try to dance the girls' one, please try to dance the girls' one on youtube for all of you lucky people.
I'm scared of seniors.
Please do.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Thank you very much.
If you think this video is good, if you think Misaki-chan and Kina-chan worked hard in the cold, please give us a high rating, subscribe to our channel, and comment.
Bye.
This time we are wearing costumes by D-Holic!